http://www.chelmsford.anglican.org/data-protection-and-privacy

> Jenny Tomlinsons Audio
> How will it work?
> What will it mean?
> Safe Spaces
Transforming the communities of Essex & East London through Christ’s presence
Data Protection and Privacy
Data Protection and Privacy
The Chelmsford Diocesan Board of Finance (CDBF) commits to complying with the Data Protection Act 2018 and takes the privacy of personal data very seriously.
Like any organisation the CDBF needs to process personal data in order to fulfil it's legitimate purposes, principally the furtherance of the mission and ministry of the Anglican Church in Essex and East London. Each organisation is to have a document, known as a Privacy Notice, the purpose of which is to explain to people how and why their data is being processed. Our General Privacy Notice can be downloaded from the link further down the page. This privacy notice explains the processing of personal data for clergy, licensed and authorised lay ministers, parish officers and other parish role holders, school contacts and other some other key contacts and therefore covers the majority of processing of personal data. .
The CDBF is quite a broad and diverse organisation and therefore there are some areas of our work which have dedicated privacy notices in order to better explain the processing of personal data in each context. These can also be downloaded by clicking on the links below.  These notices are being kept under regular review and the most recent versions will be uploaded to this webpage, so please do check this webpage periodically.
General Privacy Notice
Safeguarding Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice (e-bulletin)
Diocesan Retreat House, Pleshey
Website privacy policy
Who should I contact if I have a question?
Our aim is to be as open and transparent on our data processing as possible. If you have any queries or concerns about the processing of your personal data, please contact our Data Protection Coordinator, Nathan Whitehead through one of the routes below:
email: dataprotection@chelmsford.anglican.org
telephone: 01245 294412.
post: 53 New Street, Chelmsford, CM1 1AT
Should you wish to contact the Information Commissioners Office, they can be contacted through the following routes:
Address: Information Commissioner’s Office, Wycliffe House, Water Lane, Wilmslow, Cheshire, SK9 5AF
Email: https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/email, or Phone: 0303 123 1133
For more information please contact Nathan Whitehead
Is there anything wrong with this page?
